# M. Rafli Agusta Rizalfa

# Fullstack Developer

**L**+6285764278342

LinkedIn

Portofolio

Fresh graduate of Informatics Engineering from the Sumatera Institute of Technology, I have over a year's experience in web and mobile development, especially in Laravel, Go, React Native, and Flutter. I am also proficient in IT Support, capable of maintaining and troubleshooting both hardware and software.

### **Experience**

#### PT Binokular Media Utama - Front End Developer & Data Analyst

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

- · Analyzing bunch of data using Python and storing it to the SQL Database
- Visualize data using chart.js and Laravel Framework.
- Implementing Microservice concept using RabbitMQ.
- Collaborate with the Editorial and Editorial teams.

#### PT Andalas Media Group - Fullstack Developer

Dec 2022 - July 2023

- Created an online news media website for the Tulang Bawang Barat region (local) for PT Andalas Media Group.
- Developed with Laravel Bootstrap Framework, and using the Rich Editor API from CKEditor.
- Implemented SDLC Modified Waterfall and deploying and maintaining the system.

#### Sumatera Institute of Technology (ITERA) - Lecture Assistant

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

- Training the basics of website programming such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL.
- Training how the internet and websites work.
- Mentored students who are developing projects for clients.
- Training SDLC and SSDLC as well as working with sprints and monitoring sprint progress.
- Managed relationships with stakeholders run well until the project is completed.

Freelance Jan 2024 - Now

- develop mobile applications or websites according to client requests.
- using development tools such as React Native and Flutter to create mobile applications
- using Laravel or Go for backend.
- using HTML, CSS, JS & PHP for Front End Web development.

#### Education

#### Sumatera Institute of Technology

Aug 2019 - Jan 2024

• Bachelor of Informatic Engineering with GPA: 3.16

#### Skills

Laravel

• Flutter

• HTML

• SQL

• Go

• React Native

• CSS

• Git/Github/Gitlab

## **Project**

Myanimelist App Clone

Recreating Myanimelist mobile App using React Native framework and integration with Jikan API. Also implementing function such as search, watchlist, sorting etc.

• Kia Computer (Web based E-commerce)

create a website for a computer shop located in the Bandar Lampung area.
Using HTML CSS and JS on Frontend development, and Golang on Backend development.